<featured>

<comic><title>Star Veil</title>
<image>http://www.panelflow.com/comics/S/Star_Veil/images/comicthumb.jpg</image><description>Follow the toughest group of ex-Rangers known as the Rats, as they keep the balance of good vs evil on the rim worlds of the galaxy, helping keep the secrets of our past, and the keys to our future in the hands of the Good Guys.</description><link>http://www.needcomics.com/Star_Veil/</link></comic>

<comic><title>Spam Kills</title><image>http://www.panelflow.com/comics/S/Spam_Kills/images/comicthumb.jpg</image><description>Follow the lives of the Stupid Users cast before the Zombie outbreak as they battle it out with the hordes of iWar and fight the hordes of stupid users at their door. Just an Un-Ordinary day in I.T.</description><link>http://www.needcomics.com/Spam_Kills/</link></comic>

<comic><title>The Path</title><image>http://www.panelflow.com/comics/T/The_Path/images/comicthumb.jpg</image><description>The story of the supposed reincarnation of a certain 'Once and Future King' chosen by the gods of Mankind to wage a rather solitary war against the inter dimensional horrors of H.P. Lovecraft's Cthulhu Mythos because...well...no one else will do it. With a rusty old sword and questionable allies at his side, can Chance McGavin actually turn back the tide of darkness...or are we all doomed?</description><link>http://www.needcomics.com/The_Path/</link></comic>

<comic><title>Fafnir the Dragon</title><image>http://www.panelflow.com/comics/F/Fafnir_The_Dragon/images/comicthumb.jpg</image><description>Mightier than a god, dumber than a rock.  While searching for his stolen treasure, history's greatest dragon is hurled into an apocalyptic future where he and talk-show host Jon Stewart must battle hordes of slavering mutants, prevent the assassination of Barack Obama and save earth from an Al-Qaeda super-virus!</description><link>http://www.arcanacomics.com/fafnir</link></comic>


<comic><title>Mohagen</title><image>http://www.panelflow.com/comics/M/Mohagen/images/comicthumb.jpg</image><description>Mohagen is like most goldfish; he's trapped in a two-gallon universe with only an elitist cat and a philosophical piece of aquarium decoration for company, his only window into the outside world is that of 12-year-old boy who routinely torments him, and he is obsessed with delusions of escape and evolution. He is also orange and 'fancy'.</description><link>http://www.needcomics.com/Mohagen/</link></comic>



</featured>